{
    "id": "seaketa",
    "name": "seaketa",
    "yomi": "シーケタ",
    "text": [
        "I do music things.",
        "音楽やっています。"
    ],
    "link": [
        {
            "a": "Bandcamp",
            "href": "https://kumocommunication.bandcamp.com"
        },
        {
            "a": "Twitter",
            "href": "https://www.twitter.com/seaketaseaketa/"
        },
        {
            "a": "SoundCloud",
            "href": "https://www.soundcloud.com/seaketa/"
        }
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "Q1",
            "question": "Which is your favorite ear?",
            "jp": "好きな耳は？",
            "yes": "right",
            "left": "右",
            "no": "left",
            "right": "左"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q2",
            "question": "Do you like glasses?",
            "jp": "メガネは好き？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q3",
            "question": "a jewelry",
            "jp": "宝石",
            "yes": "I want one.",
            "left": "欲しい",
            "no": "I don't want it.",
            "right": "欲しくない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q4",
            "question": "I {　　} some sign",
            "jp": "気配を",
            "yes": "feel",
            "left": "感じる",
            "no": "don't feel",
            "right": "感じない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q5",
            "question": "When you find a stone",
            "jp": "石を見かけたら",
            "yes": "you'd kick it",
            "left": "蹴る",
            "no": "you wouldn'd kick it",
            "right": "蹴らない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q6",
            "question": "Do you like sound of gravel?",
            "jp": "砂利の音",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "好き",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "嫌い"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q7",
            "question": "I {　　} to talk more with others?",
            "jp": "人と",
            "yes": "want",
            "left": "しゃべりたい",
            "no": "don't want",
            "right": "しゃべりたくない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q8",
            "question": "Which do you prefer?",
            "jp": "山か海どっちが好き",
            "yes": "the mountain",
            "left": "山",
            "no": "the ocean",
            "right": "海"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q9",
            "question": "Speaking of water flowing",
            "jp": "水が流れるといえば",
            "yes": "The river",
            "left": "川",
            "no": "The waterfall",
            "right": "滝"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q10",
            "question": "Have you ever picked up a stone?",
            "jp": "石を拾ったことが",
            "yes": "Yes I have.",
            "left": "ある",
            "no": "No I haven't.",
            "right": "ない"
        }
    ]
}